Guide to the Abe Fortas Papers
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Correspondence and Topical Files, 1935-1983; Series II
  - Lazarus, Ralph, 1961-1981 (Box 116, Folder 263)
    See also: Porter, Paul A. and Kathleen Winsor; Series IV. Inaugural Concert 1965; Lazarus family
  - Lazarus, Simon, Jr., 1960-1967 (Box 116, Folder 264)
    See also: Series III. Speeches--Justifications Under the Robinson-Patman Act, University of Cincinnati College of Law; Series IV. Lazarus family
  - Le, 1958-1977 (Box 116, Folder 265)
  - Leahy, Patrick J.
  - Lebensohn, Zigmond M., 1956-1962 (Box 116, Folder 266)
    See also: Series III. Speeches--Insanity and the Law, University of Chicago
  - Lehner family, 1967-1982 (Box 116, Folder 267 - 271)
    See also: Casals, Pablo and Marta; Douglas, William O.--Memorial service, Supreme Court of the United States [Memorial Resolutions]; Kollek, Teddy; Peru trip; Series III. Articles--"The Case Against Capital Punishment"; Speeches--[No title], Judicial Conference of the First Circuit, 1968; The Generations, Northeastern University, Boston, Massachusetts
  - Leventhal, Harold, [ca. 1960]-1980 (Box 116, Folder 272)
    See also: Charitable contributions
  - Lever Brothers, 1956-1972 (Box 116, Folder 273)
    See also: de Baat, M.G.; Heyworth, Geoffrey and Laurence; Macrory family; Rykens, Paul; Series III. Articles--"'Anti-trust' in the United States"; Series IV. 1964 Presidential campaign--Groups for LBJ; United Way
  - Levi, Edward H.
    See: Douglas, William O.--"Inquiry into the State of Individual Freedom"; Marcus, Stanley and family; Series III. Speeches--Insanity and the Law, University of Chicago; Implications of Durham's Case, American Psychiatric Association; Series IV. Arnold, Thurman Wesley; Series VI. University of Chicago, School of Law; Washington School of Psychiatry
  - Levin, A. Leo
  - Lewis, Anthony
    See: Douglas, William O.--Douglas Anniversary Convocation; Gideon, Clarence Earl; Le
  - Li-Ly, 1957-1981 (Box 116, Folder 274)
  - Licensing Executives Society, 1977-1980 (Box 117, Folder 275)
  - Life Magazine, 1968-1969 (Box 117, Folder 276)
  - Lin, Paul T. K., 1979-1980 (Box 117, Folder 277)
  - Linden, Bella L., 1976-1981 (Box 117, Folder 278)
    See also: Casals, Pablo and Marta; Douglas, William O.--Memorial service; Schneider, Alexander; Stern, Isaac and Vera; Series VI. Kennedy Center, Labor; Executive Committee
  - Linn, James P., 1975-1982 (Box 117, Folder 279)
  - Linowitz, Sol M. New York Times; Series VI. Synagogue Council of America, Bicentennial Committee; Kennedy Center Productions, Inc., [ca. 1965]-1977 (Box 117, Folder 280)
    See also: Johnson, Lady Bird; Johnson, Lyndon Baines; Series III. Speeches--"Lyndon Johnson"
  - Loeb, John L., 1965-1973 (Box 117, Folder 281)
    See also: Douglas, William O.--Memorial service, Supreme Court of the United States [Memorial Resolutions]; Hessler, Curtis Alan; Israel trip; Johnson, Lyndon Baines; Porter, Paul A. and Kathleen Winsor; Series III. Books-- Concerning Dissent and Civil Disobedience, Correspondence (personal), L-R; Articles--"The Frontier Between Antitrust Law and the Securities Market"; "Lyndon Johnson"; "The Constitution and the Presidency"; Speeches--The Securities Industry and Washington--1971, The Round Table, Colorado Springs, Colorado; The Social and Political Attitudes Affecting Washington Regulation of Wall Street, Investment Association of New York; The Investment Environment: The Legislative and Regulatory Framework, The Conference Board; Series VI. Kennedy Center Productions, Inc.
  - Long, Russell B.
  - Looney, Everett L., 1956 (Box 117, Folder 282)
  - Louchheim, Katie [with interview notes], 1981 (Box 117, Folder 283)
  - Luckman, Charles, 1960-1961 (Box 117, Folder 284)
    See also: Series III. Speeches--A Perspective of Labor-Management Relations, Rutgers Labor Institute; Series IV. Correspondence--Personal--H-L
  - Mac-Ma, 1956-1981 (Box 117, Folder 285)
  - MacLeish, Archibald
  - MacLeod, Frances A., 1956-1968 (Box 117, Folder 286)
    See also: Series IV. Correspondence--Personal--Mac-R
  - Macrory family, 1956-1973 (Box 117, Folder 287)
    See also: Series III. Articles--"America's Electrical Price Conspiracy"; Speeches--The Grievances of the Small Business Man -- A Bill of Particulars, American Bar Association Section on Antitrust Laws; Series VI. Institute of Judicial Administration, Project on Anglo-American Administrative Law
  - Maggin, Donald L., 1960-1961 (Box 117, Folder 288)
  - Mance, Henry S.
    See: Bogan, Eugene F.
  - Mann, Theodore
    See: Schneider, Alexander
  - Marcus, Stanley and family, 1956-1982 (Box 117, Folder 289 - 291)
    See also: Douglas, William O.; Johnson, Lyndon Baines; Series III. Books-- Concerning Dissent and Civil Disobedience, Correspondence (personal), L-R; Articles--"'Anti-trust' in the United States"; Speeches--"The Art of Living Together," City College of New York; Series IV. Kennedy assassination, John F.; Series VI. Kennedy Center, Honors Gala; Poole, Jillian; Federated Department Stores
  - Marlboro Music Festival
    See: Cousins, Norman; T; Series VI. Marlboro School of Music
  - Marlboro Music School
    See: Schneider, Alexander; Serkin, Rudolph; Si-So
  - Marshall, Thurgood, 1970-1980 (Box 117, Folder 292)
    See also: Krim, Arthur and Mathilde; Series III. Speeches--[No title], Federal Trial Examiners
  - Mastroianni, Thomas, 1978 (Box 117, Folder 293)
  - Mathias, Charles Mc. C., Jr.
    See: Charitable contributions; Douglas, William O.--"Inquiry into the State of Individual Freedom"
  - Mazur, Paul M., 1963-1971 (Box 117, Folder 294)
    See also: Series III. Books-- Concerning Dissent and Civil Disobedience, Correspondence (personal), L-R; Speeches--[No title], Alumni Law Day dinner, Boston College Law School; Series IV. Correspondence--Personal--Mac-R
  - Mc, 1957-1981 (Box 117, Folder 295)
  - McCree, Wade H., Jr.
  - McGovern, George, 1972-1980 (Box 117, Folder 296)
  - McGuire, Rebekah L., 1957-1977 (Box 118, Folder 297)
  - McKay, Robert B.
    See: Douglas, William O.--"Inquiry into the State of Individual Freedom"; Series III. Speeches--Equal Rights--For Whom?, James Madison Lecture, New York University School of Law; The Fourteenth Amendment and Equality Under Law, New York University School of Law
  - McNally, James W. and family, 1960-1963 (Box 118, Folder 298)
  - McNamara, Pat
    See: Ketcham, Orman W.
  - McWilliams, Carey
    See: Douglas, William O.; Fortes, Meyer and family
  - Me, 1957-1981 (Box 118, Folder 299)
  - Methot, Frederic A.
    See: Agger, Donald
  - Metzenbaum, Howard M.
  - Mi-Mo, 1956-1981 (Box 118, Folder 300)
  - Middleton, Harry J.
    See: Johnson, Lyndon Baines, LBJ Library
  - Miller, Merle
    See: Johnson, Lady Bird
  - Mitchell, Maurice B.
  - Mitchell, Stephen A.
  - Montoni, Raymond, 1958-1965 (Box 118, Folder 301)
  - Morse, Wayne
  - Moscoso, Teodoro
    See: Agger, Donald; Casals, Pablo and Marta; Mi-Mo; Muñoz Marín, Luis; Puerto Rico; Series IV. Puerto Rico, Laboy, Luis; Series VI. Carnegie Hall Corporation and Society
  - Moyers, William, [ca. 1963]-1969 (Box 118, Folder 302)
  - Mu, 1960-1981 (Box 118, Folder 303)
  - Muller, Theodor, 1956-1981 (Box 118, Folder 304)
    See also: Agger, Carolyn E.; Series VI. Kennedy Center; Studio/Terrace Theater
  - Mumford, Milton C.
    See: Lever Brothers
  - Muñoz Marín, Luis [includes photographs], 1959-1982 (Box 118, Folder 305 - 307)
    See also: Benítez, Jaime and family; Puerto Rico; Rostow, Eugene V.; Series III. Articles--"Sacco, Vanzetti--and Justice"; Speeches--An Appreciation: 1968 Freedom House Award to Pablo Casals, New York, New York
  - Murchison, Clint, Jr.
    See: Johnson, Lyndon Baines; Mu
  - Murphy, Stanley, 1968 (Box 118, Folder 308)
  - Murrow, Edward R.
  - Music, 1961-1982 (Box 118, Folder 309 - 311)
    See also: Ca; J; Ka; Montoni, Raymond; Pittman, Roy Labon; Wa-We
  - Na-Ne, 1961-1982 (Box 118, Folder 312)
  - Nathan, Robert R., 1958-1961 (Box 118, Folder 313)
  - National Chamber Orchestra Institute
  - Navasky, Victor S., 1970-1982 (Box 118, Folder 314)
  - Neal, Phil C.
    See: Alschuler, Martha F.; Douglas, William O.--Memorial service; Friedman & Koven, personal correspondence; Na-Ne; Saltzman, Herbert; Young, Lawrence A.; Series VI. University of Chicago Law School
  - New School Concerts
    See: Charitable contributions; Schneider, Alexander; Series VI. Kennedy Center, General correspondence
  - Ni-Nu, 1956-1971 (Box 119, Folder 315)
  - Nikoloric, L. A.
    See: Ketcham, Orman W.; Ni-Nu
  - Nixon, Richard M.
    See: Bogan, Eugene F.; Ni-Nu; Sa-Sc; Series VI. Kennedy Center, General correspondence
  - O, 1958-1975 (Box 119, Folder 316)
  - Oehlert, Benjamin H., Jr., 1965-1973 (Box 119, Folder 317)
    See also: Series III. Articles--"Thurman Arnold and the Theater of Law"; Speeches--Law Day, Emory University
  - Pa-Pe, 1958-1982 (Box 119, Folder 318)
  - Palestine, 1947-1973 (Box 119, Folder 319 - 320)
  - Paul, Randolph
    See: Applications for admissions to courts; Paul, Weiss, Rifkind, Wharton & Garrison
  - Paul, Weiss, Rifkind, Wharton & Garrison, 1956-1981 (Box 119, Folder 321)
    See also: Hessler, Curtis Alan
  - Pell, Claiborne
    See: Charitable contributions; Series IV. Cultural activities in the White House; National Council on the Arts--general materials; National Council on the Arts--legislative materials
  - Pendergast, Martin, 1959-1967 (Box 119, Folder 322)
    See also: Douglas, William O.; Heyworth, Geoffrey and Laurence; Lever Brothers
  - Pepper, Claude
  - Percy, Charles H., 1972-1981 (Box 119, Folder 323)
    See also: Charitable contributions; Johnson, Lyndon Baines; Series VI. Kennedy Center, General correspondence
  - Peru trip, 1979-1982 (Box 119, Folder 324 - 325)
  - Pf-Pr, 1956-1981 (Box 119, Folder 326)
  - Philip Morris, Inc., 1960-1966 (Box 119, Folder 327)
    See also: Series IV. 1964 Presidential campaign--Contributions
  - Phillips, Howard, 1959-1972 (Box 119, Folder 328)
  - Pittman, Roy Labon, 1980-1981 (Box 120, Folder 329)
  - Pollak, Louis H., 1966-1980 (Box 120, Folder 330)
    See also: Burson, Harold and family; Douglas, William O.--"Inquiry into the State of Individual Freedom"; Yale Law School; Yale University library; Series III. Articles--"Thurman Arnold and the Theater of Law"; Speeches--[No title], Yale Law Journal banquet, 1966; Prayer Breakfast, American College of Trial Lawyers
  - Porter, Paul A., 1947-1975 (Box 120, Folder 331)
    See also: American University, Washington College of Law; Gideon, Clarence Earl; Lazarus, Fred, Jr.; Macrory family; Series III. Articles--"The Constitution and the Presidency"; Speeches--Portents for New Anti-Trust Policy, Corporate Counsel Institute; Take It Up With Gus, Herbert H. Lehman Human Relations Award Dinner, American Jewish Committee; The Social and Political Attitudes Affecting Washington Regulation of Wall Street, Investment Association of New York; Series IV. Advisory Council on the Arts; Correspondence--Personal--Mac-R; Gray, Gordon; 1964 Presidential campaign--Contributions
  - Porter, Paul A. and Kathleen Winsor, 1975-1981 (Box 120, Folder 332 - 334)
    See also: Douglas, William O.--Douglas Anniversary Convocation, Memorial service; Series III. Articles-- Go East Young Man: The Early Years, by William O. Douglas
  - Presidential impoundment of funds, 1973 (Box 120, Folder 335 - 336)
  - Prettyman, E. Barrett, Jr.
    See: Charitable contributions; Series VI. Administrative Conference of the United States, Committee on Personnel
  - Probst, Raymond R.
    See: music; Pf-Pr
  - Puerto Rico, 1958-1969 (Box 120, Folder 337)
    See also: Benítez, Jaime and family; González, Pedro A.; Hernández-Colón, Rafael; Mi-Mo; Na-Ne
  - Purcell, Ganson
  - Ra-Ri, 1956-1981 (Box 120, Folder 338)
  - Rabin, Yitzhak
  - Raymont, Henry, 1966-1981 (Box 120, Folder 339)
    See also: Benítez, Jaime and family; Johnson, Lyndon Baines; Krim, Arthur and Mathilde; Montoni, Raymond
  - Reed, Stanley.
    See: Rogers, William D
  - Reich, Charles A., 1960-1970 (Box 120, Folder 340)
    See also: Porter, Paul A.; Series III. Speeches--The Rule in Durham's Case, Federal Bar Association; Doing Business Under the Robinson-Patman Act: Brokerage, Advertising Allowances, and Services, Practising Law Institute
  - Resignation, letters of, 1965-1966 (Box 120, Folder 341)
  - Reynolds, Dana D.
    See: International Center for Dynamics of Development
  - Ribicoff, Abraham
    See: Arnold, Thurman Wesley; Ra-Ri; Stern, Isaac and Vera
  - Richardson, Margaret S., 1976 (Box 120, Folder 342)
  - Rifkind, Simon H.
    See: Douglas, William O.--Supreme Court of the United States [Memorial Resolutions]; Kaplan, J. M. and family; Palestine; Paul, Weiss, Rifkind, Wharton & Garrison
  - Rioch, David McKenzie and Margaret Jeffrey, 1967-1982 (Box 120, Folder 343)
    See also: Series III. Speeches--[No title], Animal Welfare Institute; Series IV. Correspondence--Personal--Mac-R; Series VI. Judicial Conference of the United States Court of Appeals for the District of Columbia Circuit, Mental disorders; Marlboro School of Music; Washington School of Psychiatry
  - Ripley, S. Dillon, 1966-1978 (Box 120, Folder 344)
    See also: Hirshhorn, Joseph H.; Johnson, Lyndon Baines; Ra-Ri; Series VI. Kennedy Center
  - Rob-Ron, 1958-1981 (Box 121, Folder 345)
  - Robb, Charles ("Chuck") S. and Linda Bird
    See: Johnson, Lady Bird; Series III. Books-- Concerning Dissent and Civil Disobedience, Correspondence (personal), L-R; Speeches--[No title], Student Legal Forum, University of Virginia School of Law, 1971
  - Rockefeller, John D. ("Jay"), IV
    See: Percy, Charles H.
  - Rodell, Fred, 1945-1980 (Box 121, Folder 346)
    See also: Series III. Articles--"Thurman Arnold and the Theater of Law"
  - Rodon, Miriam Naveira de, 1977-1979 (Box 121, Folder 347)
  - Rogers, M. Robert, 1966-1972 (Box 121, Folder 348)
    See: Kreeger, David Lloyd
  - Rogers, William D., 1956-1966 (Box 121, Folder 349)
    See also: Puerto Rico; Trías Monge, José; Series III. Speeches--Methods of Committees Investigating Subversion: A Critique
  - Rogers, William P.
  - Roncalio, Teno
    See also: Scott-Grant House
  - Roo-Ros, 1956-1972 (Box 121, Folder 350)
  - Roosevelt, Eleanor
    See: Series III. Speeches--An Approach to Progressive Policy, Southwestern College at Memphis; Series V. United Nations--Trusteeship; Series VI. President's Committee on Equal Employment Opportunity
  - Roosevelt, Franklin D., Jr.
    See: Rostow, Eugene V.; Series IV. Puerto Rico, Laboy, Luis; Series VI. Roosevelt, Eleanor, Memorial Foundation
  - Rosenblatt, William
  - Rosenbloom, H. David, 1966-1978 (Box 121, Folder 351)
  - Rostow, Eugene V., 1946-1976 (Box 121, Folder 352)
    See also: Benítez, Jaime and family; Douglas, William O.; Puerto Rico; Series III. Books-- Concerning Dissent and Civil Disobedience, Correspondence (personal), L-R; Series IV. Arnold, Thurman Wesley; Johnston, Paul
  - Rostow, Walt W.
    See: Burson, Harold and family
  - Rot-Row, 1956-1982 (Box 121, Folder 353)
  - Rothschild, Alain de
  - Rowe, James H., Jr.
    See: Puerto Rico; Rot-Row; Series III. Speeches--[No title], Constitution Day, San Juan, Puerto Rico; Series IV. Correspondence--Personal--Mac-R; Lazarus family
  - Royall, Kenneth C., 1968 (Box 121, Folder 354)
  - Ru-Ry [includes photograph], 1946-1981 (Box 121, Folder 355)
  - Rubin, Seymour J., 1957-1970 (Box 121, Folder 356)
    See also: Agger, Donald; Charitable contributions; Woodfin, Gene M. and Judith; Series III. Speeches--[No title], American Friends of the Hebrew University
  - Ruebhausen, Oscar M.
    See: Series VI. Russell Sage Foundation
  - Rudnai, Judith A., 1970-1979 (Box 121, Folder 357)
  - Rutledge, Wiley
    See: Ru-Ry
  - Rykens, Paul, 1953-1962 (Box 121, Folder 358)
  - Sa-Sc, 1955-1982 (Box 121, Folder 359)
  - Sabin, Albert B.
    See: Bloch, Ernest and family; Sa-Sc
  - Saldaña, Lino J., 1956-1973 (Box 121, Folder 360)
  - Salk, Jonas
    See: Sa-Sc
  - Saltonstall, John L., Jr.
  - Salzman, Herbert [includes photograph], 1966-1981 (Box 121, Folder 361)
    See also: Series IV. Abell, Bess; Correspondence--Personal--S-Z; 1964 Presidential campaign--Contributions; Series VI. Kennedy Center, Stevens, Roger L.; Studio/Terrace Theater; Kennedy Center Productions, Inc.
  - Sánchez-Vilella, Roberto, 1956-1973 (Box 121, Folder 362)
    See also: Cooper, Evelyn N.; Puerto Rico; Series VI. Federated Department Stores
  - Sand, René, 1968 (Box 145, Folder 223)
  - Scheuer, James H., 1958-1981 (Box 121, Folder 363)
    See also: Charitable contributions; Scott-Grant House; Stern, Isaac and Vera; Series IV. Correspondence--Personal--S-Z; President's Council of Economic Advisers; Series VI. President's Committee on Equal Employment Opportunity
  - Schneider, Alexander, 1961-1982 (Box 121, Folder 364 - 365)
    See also: Casals, Pablo and Marta; Linden, Bella L.; Ripley, S. Dillon;Series IV.Marlboro Music Festival; Series VI. Carnegie Hall Corporation and Society
  - Schuster, M. Lincoln, 1949
  - Schwartz, Bernard
    See: Warren, Earl; Series III. Speeches--The Fourteenth Amendment and Equality Under Law, New York University School of Law; Series VI. Institute of Judicial Administration, Project on Anglo-American Administrative Law
  - Schwartz, Louis B., 1966-1967 (Box 122, Folder 366)
  - Schwede, Walter, 1977-1981 (Box 122, Folder 367)
  - Scott, Andrea K., 1976 (Box 122, Folder 368)
  - Scott-Grant House, 1975-1976 (Box 122, Folder 369 - 370)
  - Se-Sh, 1960-1981 (Box 122, Folder 371)
  - Segal, Bernard G., 1967-1980 (Box 122, Folder 372)
    See also: Douglas, William O.--"Inquiry into the State of Individual Freedom," Supreme Court of the United States [Memorial Resolutions]; Series III. Speeches--The Training of the Practitioner, Rutgers University, School of Law; [No title], Jewish Theological Seminary; Prayer Breakfast, American College of Trial Lawyers; Law Day, Memphis State University School of Law; [No title], Justice Lodge, Anti-Defamation League of B'nai Brith; Series VI. Institute of Judicial Administration, Project on Anglo-American Administrative Law; Judicial Conference of the United States, Advisory Committee on Appellate Rules
  - Serkin, Peter
  - Serkin, Rudolph, 1966-1978 (Box 122, Folder 373)
    See also: Series III. Speeches--[No title], Justice Lodge, Anti-Defamation League of B'nai Brith; Series IV. Marlboro Music Festival; Series VI. Kennedy Center, Honors Gala; Studio/Terrace Theater; Marlboro School of Music
  - Sevareid, Eric
    See: Douglas, William O.--"Inquiry into the State of Individual Freedom," Memorial service; Series III. Speeches--Checks and Balances--Or Checkmate? A Bicentennial Summation, College of Mount St. Joseph
  - Seward, Ralph T.
    See: Douglas, William O.--Memorial service
  - Shalala, Donna E.
  - Shapiro, Samuel H.
  - Shulman, Harry
    See: Yale Law School
  - Si-So, 1956-1982 (Box 122, Folder 374)
  - Sills, Beverly.
    See: Linn, James P.
  - Simon, John G.
  - Slaff, George
    See: Douglas, William O.--Memorial service; Si-So; Series III. Speeches--[No title], Constitutional Rights Foundation; [No title], University of Southern California, 1968
  - Slocombe, Walter B., 1968-1978 (Box 122, Folder 375)
    See also: Series III. Speeches--"Lyndon Johnson," New York Times
  - Slome, Ansel A., 1977-1979 (Box 122, Folder 376)
  - Slome, Cecil, 1962-1981 (Box 122, Folder 377)
  - Slome, Clara, 1965-1968 (Box 122, Folder 378)
  - Slome, Mary and Robert, 1961-1981 (Box 122, Folder 379)
  - Smith, Charles E., 1966-1979 (Box 122, Folder 380)
    See also: Stern, Isaac and Vera; Series III. Speeches--[No title], Convocation, Jewish Theological Seminary, 1965; Series IV. Correspondence--Personal--S-Z
  - Snyder, A. Cecil and Wanda G., 1956-1971 (Box 122, Folder 381)
    See also: Douglas, William O.--Memorial service; Gideon, Clarence Earl; Puerto Rico
  - Sonnenberg, Benjamin, 1956-1968 (Box 122, Folder 382)
    See also: Douglas, William O.; Series III. Books-- Concerning Dissent and Civil Disobedience, Correspondence (personal), S-U; Articles--"Outside the Law"; Speeches--The Art of Living Together, City College of New York; The Role of Counsel for the Witness in a Public Investigation, Harvard Student Bar Association; Series VI. Federated Department Stores
  - Southwestern College at Memphis, 1966-1983 (Box 122, Folder 383)
    See also: Charitable contributions; Pf-Pr
  - Sp-Sy, 1956-1982 (Box 122, Folder 384)
  - Spater, George A., 1963-1971 (Box 123, Folder 385)
    See also: Stern, Isaac and Vera;Series III.Books-- Concerning Dissent and Civil Disobedience, Correspondence (personal), S-U
  - St. Clair, James D.
  - Stangl, Debra
    See: Douglas, William O.--Memorial service; Sp-Sy
  - Stark, Margaret
    See: Trampler, Walter and Margaret Stark
  - Steinem, Gloria, 1971 (Box 123, Folder 386)
  - Steinway, Frederick
    See: Agger, Donald; Series IV. Advisory Council on the Arts
  - Stern, Isaac and Vera [includes photographs], 1957-1981 (Box 123, Folder 387 - 392)
    See also: American-Israel Cultural Foundation; Casals, Pablo and Marta; Douglas, William O.--"Inquiry into the State of Individual Freedom," Memorial service; Kaplan, J. M. and family; Music; Ripley, S. Dillon; Spater, George A.; Series III. Speeches--[No title], Convocation, Jewish Theological Seminary, 1965; [No title], Bar-Ilan University, New York, New York; Series VI. Carnegie Hall Corporation and Society; Fund for Higher Education (in Israel)
  - Stevens, Christine and Roger, 1964-1982 (Box 123, Folder 393)
    See also: Bloch, Ernest and family; Casals, Pablo and Marta; Kaplan, J. M. and family; Stern, Isaac and Vera; Series III. Speeches--[No title], Animal Welfare Institute; [No title], Albert Schweitzer Medal Award presentation to Senator Warren G. Magnuson and Senator A. S. Mike Monroney, Animal Welfare Institute; [No title], The Johnson Foundation, Racine, Wisconsin; Series IV. Cultural activities in the White House
  - Stewart, Potter, 1966-1981 (Box 123, Folder 394)
    See also: Series III. Books-- Concerning Dissent and Civil Disobedience, Correspondence (personal), S-U; Speeches--[No title], Yale Law Journal banquet, 1966
  - Stroock, Alan M.
  - Sturges, Wesley A.
    See: Arnold, Thurman Wesley; Yale Law School, Course in "Legal Principles of Competitive Economics"; Series III. Speeches--"An Approach to Progressive Policy," Southwestern College at Memphis
  - SuCrest Corporation [includes photograph], 1957-1972 (Box 123, Folder 395)
    See also: Series III. Books-- Concerning Dissent and Civil Disobedience, Correspondence (personal), S-U
  - Sutherland, Arthur E.
    See: Katzenbach, Nicholas deB.
  - Suttice, Bobby D., 1972-1973 (Box 123, Folder 396)
  - Symington, James W., 1965-1974 (Box 123, Folder 397)
    See also: Charitable contributions; Johnson, Lady Bird; Karsten, Thomas L.; Slome, Cecil
  - Symington, Stuart, 1956-1970 (Box 123, Folder 398)
    See also: Agger, Donald; Series III. Speeches--[No title], Animal Welfare Institute
  - T, 1956-1981 (Box 123, Folder 399)
  - Taussig, Richard S.
    See: SuCrest Corporation; Series VI. Federated Department Stores
  - Team Defense Project, 1977 (Box 123, Folder 400)
  - Tennery, B. J.
    See: American University, Washington College of Law; Series III. Speeches--[No title], Edwin A. Mooers Lecture, Washington College of Law, American University
  - Toro, Ademar
  - Trampler, Walter and Margaret Stark, 1961-1980, undated (Box 123, Folder 401)
    See also: Hummel, Jerri Roberts Shafer; Kaplan, J. M. and family; Series IV. Inaugural Concert 1965
  - Travel itineraries and receipts, 1941-1947 (Box 123, Folder 402)
  - Trías Monge, José
  - Tsai, C. L., 1972-1982 (Box 124, Folder 405)
  - Tweedy, Gordon and Mary Johnson, 1965-1981 (Box 124, Folder 406)
  - Tydings, Joseph D., 1965-1967 (Box 124, Folder 407)